(Sheldon:)I'm starting my own convention.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, just buy
scalped tickets with us.
(Sheldon:)I told you. Buying scalped
tickets is against the rules.
(Sheldon:)If you get caught, you get
banned from Comic-Con for life.
(Sheldon:)Life, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)You're gonna feel pretty silly
when we're 80 years old,
(Sheldon:)and you have to drive me down there
(Sheldon:)and then wait in the car
for three days.
(Leonard:)Do what you want.
We're getting scalped tickets.
(Howard:)I already found a guy online
who's willing to sell.
(Sheldon:)How do you know
this isn't a sting operation
(Sheldon:)set up by the Comic-Con police?
(Leonard:)The same way I know that the people
in the TV set can't see me.
(Howard:)Sheldon, just come with us.
(Howard:)You're not gonna make
your own convention.
(Sheldon:)You know, there was a time
when Comic-Con didn't exist at all
(Sheldon:)until one lone dreamer
with a unique vision made it happen.
(Sheldon:)And you mark my words,
I'm gonna rip that guy off.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yes, I'm starting
my own comic book convention,
(Sheldon(on phone):)and I thought that your client,
Robert Downey Jr.,